I can't thank you enough, honestly.
I should thank you.
I appreciate you always calling
on me to help, Antistella.
I'll see you again soon, Noor.
Nice work today, Noor.
And thanks to you, we'll have no problem
sticking to the schedule this month.
Yeah, glad to hear it!
What's that?
Someone! Please help me!
Hey! No!
That's... huge!
Now I'm going to fly.
I'm going to fly.
When I'm on a cloud, I'll fly.
I'll fly.
I'll fly. There's nothing to say.?
What do you want?
Thank you so much for watching.
Here, drink up.
But be careful, Mom.
It might be too hot.
It's perfect. Thank you, son.
Time to feed the goats.
I'll take them to the
pasture over by the hill.
Noor, now please be careful.
I know, Mom.
I won't go any further than the big rock.
I promise.
I'll get a wild rabbit and
some nuts and seeds later.
We'll have soup.
Hold on.
I'll boil you some more water.
Noor!
What's wrong?
I'm so sorry I can't do anything for you.
But please, Noor, live the
life you wish to leave.
Soup's ready!
Mother?
Mom?
Mom!
Let's go.
Oh, my God.
Nor, it's time for bed.
What's tonight's story?
It's about an adventurer.
What's an adventurer?
Well, son, this one, with
the help of his friends,
slayed a gigantic dragon and learned
magic spells from an old sorcerer,
broke a curse upon a forest,
and even got a magic elixir
from the king of the dead.
No matter the situation,
an adventurer will raise their sword and
strike down evil for those who cannot.
Shall I start reading it then?
Yes, read it, read it!
Alright, now settle in and
get ready for adventure.
An adventurer?
But please, Norm, live
the life you wish to lead.
Don't eat it all at once, okay?
Dad, Mom, I'm going.
I'm leaving town for the first time ever.
To become an adventurer!
I'll make you proud.
Oh
Just off the main road. Thank you, sir.
This is it!
This place isn't for kids
to be hanging around.
Now get out of here.
The guards at the gate said I could be
an adventurer if I came to this place.
Don't be an idiot!
Your parents are probably worried sick.
They're dead.
Both of them.
No parents, huh?
I'm sorry to hear that,
kid Well, what's your name?
Nor Okay, nor,
let's see I take it you're heading
to the training academy for classes?
This is the first time I've ever had
a kid your age try to do it before.
What do you mean?
Okay, listen up.
Those registering with the Royal Capitals
Adventures Guild must
take lessons beforehand,
meaning you basically get
training for your job class.
Want to be an adventurer?
You've got to have some skills first.
What kind of skills?
You know, the art of combat
or magic, stuff like that.
Understood!
A swordsman.
Heroes and storybooks can slay a dragon
as big as a mountain in a single swing.
Finally
That's enough, Noor, unfortunately.
Wait, just give me some time!
Forget it.
Going further would be a waste of time.
The only thing you've retained at
all is parrying to evade an attack.
Perhaps it would be wiser if
you were to choose another path.
Who knows?
Your talent may be found
in another capacity.
Warrior.
While fighting with any weapon imaginable,
you risk your life and become
a shield for your allies.
That's pretty close to an adventurer!
I acknowledge your efforts,
but what you have
acquired is only a slight
improvement of your
natural physical abilities.
If you force yourself to continue on,
you could very well lose your life.
A hunter!
I must say, you lack the prudence to
handle any sort of delicate weaponry.
A thief!
You are unable to dismantle the trap,
nor can you sense anyone's presence,
so you cannot become a spy.
Magician!
To think you've come this far, yet
all you can manage is tiny flame.
It's extremely rare to see someone as
incapable of magic as you seem to be, Norn.
A cleric?
Although it only works on minor scratches,
it's still impressive you
became able to use low
-level healing magic
without a natural blessing.
You didn't learn one decent skill?
You spent a full
three-month term practicing
at every training school
and you didn't pass one? No.
Kid, I'm sorry.
I really am.
But I can't let you
register as an adventurer.
I don't have what it takes.
Dad? Mom?
I'm back.
It turns out I have no
talent for anything.
No.
I must take what I've learned and
train harder than I ever have before!
My swordsman instructor told me, if
you practice one skill repeatedly,
over and over, you may be able
to master another skill! Parry!
This is my skill that I acquired
in the swordsman class training.
I will train!
Morning, noon, and night!
I can repel ten swords in one go now.
I don't have any new skills
yet, but I am getting better.
It's a hundred swords in one go.
But I still haven't
acquired any new skills.
At this rate, becoming an
adventurer is nothing but a dream.
I have to try harder.
I must keep training.
These past 14 years,
I have trained every single day, and I
can now parry a thousand wooden swords.
And yet, still no worthy skills.
This is it.
One last try.
Parry, physical enhancement, feather
step, tiny small flame, low heal.
Um, are you sure this is
everything that you have to offer?
Yeah, that's all of it.
Perhaps you may be aware of the Royal
Capital's class training school system.
You can take lessons from any of
our distinguished instructors.
I know.
I've already been through all of them.
Every one?
Um, well, if that's the case, then...
I can't register with your guild, can I?
I'm truly sorry, but I re...
No, you don't need to apologize at all.
I know exactly what I can't do.
Hey, buddy.
Mind not picking on my new employee?
She just started. I'm fine. Oh, hey.
It's been a while.
I have absolutely no idea who you are.
Oh, wait a second.
You're the kid.
You're Noor.
So you mean you've been keeping up with
your own solo training this whole time?
Yeah, but in the end, I've really
only been able to improve my parrying.
Listen to me for a second.
There are different ranks of adventurers.
S-rank being the highest,
and E-rank being the lowest.
To be recognized as an E-rank, you've
got to have one or more useful skills.
But you, you don't have that.
I can't do anything but just give up, huh?
However, that does not mean
you can't be an adventurer.
Are you sure?
There's actually something
lower than E-Rank.
There he is?
The F-Rank, which is basically not talked
about, even for the people doing it.
Okay, then I can register for that one?
There are some conditions.
You're forbidden from taking
any quests that involve
killing anything or venturing
out to gather items.
What you can accept are
miscellaneous tasks around the city.
But nobody's dumb enough
to go to the trouble of
becoming an adventurer
just for running errands.
Plus, we also take a cut
for the job placement fee.
You see, it used to be a job
for beggars and vagabonds, so...
I'll do it.
You did hear what I just said, right?
Oh, I don't mind.
Let me take it on.
Then, Noor, here's your
F-Rink adventurer license.
Oh.
Thanks so much!
This means everything to me!
Thanks again!
Strength Enhancement.
Feather Step.
That was scary, huh?
Low Healing.
Tiny flame.
Stone throw.
My dream of becoming an adventurer and
being useful has finally come true.
Anything beyond this
is more than I deserve.
I'll see you again soon, Norf.
Nice work today, Noor.
And thanks to you, we'll have no problem
sticking to the schedule this month.
Yeah, glad to hear it.
Hmm?
What's that?
Someone!
Please help me!
Hey, Noor!
Oh, that's huge.
I've only seen these things in books.
I never thought they
were actually this big.
Surround it and block its movements.
We have to protect her.
Just let him get distracted!
Are you all right?
No.
He's dead.
They're all going to get killed.
Stone throw!
I've got to do it now!
It's fast!
Perry!
So much force!
One blow from that and I'm dead!
I need an opening to counterattack!
No, even if there was one,
I have no attack skills.
The girl!
She's still there!
Featherstep!
Even if I cannot become
a true adventurer hero,
I must at least be able to
protect this frightened girl.
No matter the situation, an
adventurer will raise their sword.
and strike down evil for those who cannot.
Remember, son,
that is an adventurer!
Harry!
That was close.
I would definitely have died
if that went on any longer.
And here I thought I could travel the
world and go on adventures at this level.
Yeah, right.
Um, excuse me? Hmm?
Thanks for saving me.
I'm only alive because of you.
I'm glad you survived.
Although it's too bad about them.
Um, sir, may I please have your name?
Oh, I'm not anyone important.
Hey, wait a second!
Thank God you're okay!
Yes, I'm quite safe.
I can't believe it.
I've never seen a cow like that before.
It was enormous, and so angry.
But it's clear now.
I have much more training to do.
Thank
you
so
much for watching.
Thank
you
so
much for watching.